myfreedomcreditcards.com 2017-02-24

# Privacy Policy - CreditCardSoup.com

CreditCardSoup.com is serious about protecting your online privacy. This Privacy Statement explains our views and practices concerning privacy, and how they may pertain to you as a user of our system. 

"You" or "Your" means you as a participant in or as a user of CreditCardSoup.com. "We" or "Our" or "Us" means CreditCardSoup.com. "Our site" means CreditCardSoup.com. 

**Section 1.** Collected Information 

We automatically collect and/or track the following: 

  1. web page http headers (home server domain names, IP address, type of client computer, and type of Web browser);
  2. information knowingly provided by you through on-line forms, registration forms, surveys, and or other entries, such as email addresses, personal, financial or demographic information;
  3. information, user specific or aggregate, on what pages our visitors access and
  4. the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with CreditCardSoup.com via e-mail. 

**Section 2.** Use of Data Collected 

We use your personal, demographic and profile data to enhance your experience at our site, enabling us to present content we think you might be interested in. We use your contact information to send you information about our company and promotional material from our partners. We may also use your personal, demographic and profile data to improve our site, for marketing and promotional purposes, for statistical analysis, and for editorial or feedback purposes for our advertisers. Information collected by us may be added to our databases and used for future e-mails or postal mailings regarding site updates, new products and services, upcoming events, and/or status of orders placed online. 

**Section 3.** Disclosure of Data to Third Parties 

We will only disclose to third parties information knowingly and voluntarily disclosed by you, or aggregate demographic and profile data. Any third party we share, rent, sell, or otherwise disclose data to will be carefully prescreened by us, determined by us to be reputable, and will use the personal data for marketing products and services which we determine, in our sole judgment, that you might find of interest.

This site contains links to other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. 

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

**Section 4.** Your Opt-Out Rights 

You may opt-out of receiving communications from us and or our partners when we request your information. We also allow you to remove your information from our database. If you remove your information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondences to you. You can remove your information by writing to us via postal mail at the address below, by sending an email requesting removal thru our contact form, by visiting CreditCardSoup.com and requesting your profile be deleted through our opt out procedures or by clicking [here](http://www.esunsub.com/Unsubscribe/AffProgU.asp?P=14 "Unsubscribe").

**Section 5.** Your Rights To Your Personal Data 

Upon request via postal mail or e-mail, we will provide you a summary of personal information retained by us. We will only send your personal records to your e-mail address or postal address we have on file for you. You may modify, correct, change, or update your personal record or remove your personal record from our database by contacting CreditCardSoup.com via postal mail at the address below or using our contact form.

**Section 6.** We Do Not Intend To Collect Data From Children 

The information and services provided us or our affiliates, sponsors, and advertisers are not intended to be viewed by children (under 18 years old). No information collected from children is knowingly used for any marketing or promotional purposes whatsoever, either inside or outside CreditCardSoup.com . 

**Section 7.** Our Right To Contact You 

We reserve the right to contact you regarding your account status and changes to subscriber agreements, privacy policy, or any other policies or agreements relevant to you. 

**Section 8.** Our Right To Change 

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our site. 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact us online using our  contact form or write to: 

**CreditCardSoup.com**   
P.O. Box #463  
114 N. Egan Avenue  
Madison, SD 57042 

Effective as of November 28, 2007   
Updated on April 5, 2011
